It's on, UpCami, and this time we'll be talking with Michiyo Hirai of Beyonce Seasonings and Wakana Matsumoto of Angulum.
This show will take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
We'll be taking you behind the scenes of our recording sessions and rehearsals.
I, Hirai, am currently on a spring tour.
I went to Okinawa the other day for the Okinawa show of the current spring tour.
This tour has a solo corner.
It's nice that there are only 3 soloists per show.
I sang “The Voice of the Sea”.
I love Okinawa!
Kenta Kiritani's song.
Yes, this was the first song I covered in The Ballad in 2020.
This is the first song I covered
It was the first song I performed.
At the time, no matter how much emotion I put into it, I didn't have the skills or the throat muscles to withstand expressing my emotions,
But after singing it in Okinawa four years later, I realized how much I had grown.
As the song progressed, there were many people in tears, and even in the comments on the blog, I commented for the first time. I am so glad that I worked so hard on this song, and I am so glad that I finally told people how wonderful it is.
I was so happy that I could finally tell people how wonderful this song is.
That's wonderful. Thank you very much.
Yes, well, I, Matsumoto, am on the spring tour of Angstrom, and during the last tour, I broke my shoes for the first time in my costume.
I've heard that many Angulum members had broken their shoes, but I had never broken mine.
I've never broken mine before.
I wondered how such a sturdy-looking shoe could break, but this was the first time.
The heel part of the heel came off a little bit.
The heel of the heel came off a little bit.
I was just in the middle of a song when I noticed this heel
I noticed that the heel was on my belly.
I felt like I had to do it at least a little bit.
I was trying to keep my heel from popping off too straight.
I danced while being conscious of keeping my heels straight.
It was my first experience.
I was in a hurry.
I haven't experienced it yet.
But it happens often, doesn't it?
It does happen, doesn't it?
I see it quite often.
Of course I take good care of my costumes. I take care of the costumes, of course, but...
But there are things like that, too.
I'll do my best to avoid injuries.
I'll do my best on the tour.
Now, let's take a look at the up-cameras for this tour.
First of all, let's start from here.
JuiceJuice Aiko Music Video Making
The latest single of JuiceJuice was released on May 15!
JuiceJuice's latest single
Here's a look at the making of the music video shoot for “Aiko”!
I didn't expect to see you here!
What a nice surprise!
She's crying so hard.
Wait, she's so cute!
He's so big, Mon-chan!
It's like he's taking his turn.
Beagle and Risachi look exactly alike
Risa Irie looks just like Risa
Shall I roll the camera?
You can't always blame others... only love like that.
There's a dog here, at the labyrinth.
He passed us!
A sparkling scene...
Look at this.
That was the hardest part.
I thought it was cute, but I wanted to do it this way.
I really wanted to do it.
I wanted to ask, “What's your cute name?
Okay, cut!
Well, thank you very much for the park, and thank you very much for the music, and we'll see you at the show.
Thank you very much.
Music!
We're releasing three singles this time.
And this is the last one to be shot in this order.
The tone of the song is very much like a graduation song.
I'm a little sad about it.
I don't know if Mr. Uemura himself
I think it's a little bit sad, but I think it's because Mr. Uemura himself doesn't say that he's graduating so much. To the extent that we don't really announce that we are graduating, we do not really say that we are graduating.
In the dance choreography
In the dance choreography, there are a lot of parts where Ms. Kamimura is looking around at the members.
And the members are looking at him.
I'm feeling a little sad, but I want to enjoy filming until the end.
I'm really sad, but I'm going to enjoy filming until the end.
YeahYeahYeahYeahYeahYeah
Forward Looking Backward Looking Forward Looking Backward Looking Forward Looking Backward
Totally different. Going to tomorrow.
I'm going to tomorrow. I'm going to tomorrow.
That's all right, that's all right, that's all right, that's all right, that's all right
I'll forgive you today more than you
I'm going to dance around and I'm going to forgive you
This is the last time I'm really going to shoot a music video with Mr. Kamimura.
This is the last time we're really going to shoot a music video with Mr. Uemura.
I was just thinking that this is the last time I'm really going to shoot a music video with you, Mr. Kamimura.
We haven't done any shooting together yet.
It's just the beginning.
I don't know how I feel about it.
But she doesn't seem to be feeling like she's graduating.
It might be a while before I can really feel it.
I'm thinking that today is the first step, the first step to realize it, and I'm going to do my best.
I forgive you
I'm going to chase after you and make it this way
I forgive you.
Hey, I'll forgive you too.
No customization.
Are you relieved?
Sexy.
I hate you for some reason.
I was coming up the stairs.
It's so bright, my eyes are following me.
I'd rather get a sunburn than cheer you on from tomorrow.
where I'm not helping
I'm tempted to look in the drawing with my hands and fingers
Some days I love you till meaahhhh
ahhhhh
Ohhhh! AHHHHHH!
AHHHHHHH, go! Go, go, go, go! Go, go, go, go!
Thank you!
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!
It's huge!
That's why you sneezed differently today!
No, it's not.
No.
And green is more like grass.
There's a lot of grass.
Grass?
Get away from it.
Flowers!
That's great!
Thank you!
I'm so happy! It's still here.
I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
I'm really happy! This is really great!
All right, let's get started!
Pass!
Yes, off camera, everyone smile, yes, OK.
Every day at 12:15.
That's great!
That's for sure, that's for sure.
Try putting your head on your shoulders for a second.
Do it while looking at the camera.
Yes!
I'm done, you two are done.
I think it's good. I think it's good to look at the camera.
You sure? Thank you! I think it's good! Goo first, rock, paper, scissors, goo last.
Anh, team, in, de, hoi!
Yeah!
No?
Goo at the beginning, rock, paper, scissors, goo at the end.
Part, school!
An, team, in, de, hoi! An, team, in, de, hoi!
An, team, in, de, hoi! Start! Yes, you can look at the camera.
Now, the last red cut is really a group cut, with each member interacting with the other members.
I think it really brought out the individuality of each member.
There are some scenes between the members that you haven't seen yet, so you'll have to wait for the music video to see them.
I feel relieved, I feel like I can see the future of JuiceJuice, and I've been able to see it for a long time now, so I'm sure you'll be able to feel the charm of JuiceJuice that you didn't even know they had.
I'm still working on it, so if you watch and comment a lot, I'll be very encouraged.
How was Lulu? Well, I, uh...
Well, I was the one who handed a bouquet of flowers to Mr. Kamimura, and I'm sure it was the first time for me to do that, so...
I had to stand side by side with the sub-leader-leader.
In the past one or two years, I have been working side by side with other sub-leaders.
I felt like it was my job as a sub-leader.
I felt it was my job as a sub-leader.
I felt that it was my role as a sub-leader, and that I should be the one to do it.
But the music video shooting itself was really relaxing.
But the music video shooting itself was really done in a relaxed and calm manner, with the usual JuiceJuice atmosphere.
I hope you enjoy the atmosphere of the music video.
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!
Now, I've already shown you the video.
The music itself is pretty cool.
The music itself has some rapping and the rhythm band is pretty cool, but the video is really calm.
The music itself has some rapping and the rhythm band is pretty cool, but the video seems really calm.
You said that the shooting itself was probably in February.
I heard that on the “Extra Channel” that it was shot in February.
I think it's spring-like.
It seems like spring.
I thought it might have been a warm spring-like weather.
I thought it might be the warm spring weather.
It was windy, wasn't it?
It was really appropriate to send him off
I think it was a really appropriate image to send off the guests.
Everyone looked so nice.
Everyone was wonderful.
Mr. Uemura and some of the members...
Like a group shot. Like a group shot.
Like a group shot.
I thought it was really wonderful
I was wondering how you filmed the music video
I was wondering how it was filmed.
I was wondering how they filmed the music video.
I was wondering how you filmed the music video.
I think that's why you could see the natural atmosphere of Juice Juice in the music video.
That's all for the making of Juice Juice's music video shoot.
Next, here is the making of the music video!
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 making-of video!
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 was held at Makuhari Messe on March 30th and 31st.
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024
We'll be focusing on the solos and shuffle units!
Let's take a look at the video of the making of Hello Project Hinafest 2024, which was shot on March 30 and March 31 at Makuhari Messe.
meme
me
memeTouch my heart and touch me please once again for fun
I want you to tell me everything.
Touch my heart and touch me please
You think you can do it?
You made me feel so good.
I'll take you to the fun
The dawn of the moon is full of light, rays of light together
Destiny is bright
Bless me, girl
Now touch my heart
With lots of light, even if the earth changes, my feelings won't change... me I never told anyone, so I thought I wouldn't have much luck in the shuffle unit lottery at the Hina Fest.
So I played the solo this time.
I went blank at the first moment I played it.
I was so blank at the moment when I played the solo,
When I saw the word “solo”, I was happy to sing solo on such an important stage,
But I was so happy to win!
But I was so happy that I won.
Well, this time I will be singing Morning Three's “The Garden of Love” by Otomegumi.
I had wanted to sing this song for a long time,I had wanted to sing this song for a long time,
I had been thinking of singing it at birthday events and so on,
So it was on my list from the beginning,
But the deciding factor was that I really liked the English lyrics,
I'm working hard on my language skills, so I thought it would be great if I could communicate the charm of the song on the big stage of Hina Festivals.
I'm working hard on my language skills, so I thought it would be great if I could convey that charm to the audience.
I was looking for a song with English lyrics.
I was looking for a song with English lyrics, and Ain no Sono fit the bill perfectly.
The lyrics are really cool.
The lyrics are really cool, and the range of the song is pretty easy for me to sing.
I chose this song.
Seino
I beat around the bush
I hit around
It's still difficult because it doesn't come out of my body soon
But I'm singing, me
Me.
I'm in love with you, I can't see you as me
I'm in love with you, take me, take me, take me, we, I can only remember it all, the more I want to see what it's like to be an adult.
I want to be an adult
I want to go see you.
I'm just in love with you because you're an adult.
Next time, it's at the bash
Just want to be with you
Oh, your first time?
I did my first solo. My very first solo.
Yes, I remember.
This time, Fujihiko, I didn't play it.
That's right, that's right, that's right, I didn't play it. Oh, that's right, that's right, that's right.
It was just a time when I couldn't play, I wasn't around,
So, Mr. Takamora Niinuma, a lehner of my Tsubaki Factory, played,
I didn't know him at all, and I was just at the time when Tsubaki Factory, Morning Musume, and Beyonce were on a tour together.
I don't remember which show it was, but I heard about it that morning.
I don't remember which show it was, but I was informed that morning, so I said, “Who did you think the duo was? I said, “Minami Okamura” and when I heard that she was Minami Okamura, I immediately said, “Ri Okamura”.
That's when I found out.
I didn't know who the duo was when I played.
I didn't know who the pair was yet.
I was so nervous the whole time. I've been so nervous.
Maybe a little earlier than Haru's.
directly from Ms. Shinnuma.
I was there with Rouno!
She came to me
He came to me.
From that moment on...
I was always wondering what song I should sing by myself.
But we did it once, just the two of us.
Yes, we had sung together at the 25th anniversary fan club event,
So it's like we've done it again.
When I sing with Okamura-san, I really like songs that combine cute and cool,
I thought it would be a good match. Like black and pink.
Yes, you've been saying that for a long time.
That's right. That's why I'm happy to sing such a song.
It's kind of a first for me. It was the first time for a club team unit to win.
So I don't really know what it feels like anymore, and I'm probably very nervous.
But now that I've won, I want to enjoy it as much as I can, so I'll do my best! Adult absurdity I've made eyes at you
Just want to be next to youH
Just want to be next to youHey, every time I'm so proud of you
If you're in my way tomorrow
I'm so terrible, bye-bye
Hey! Every time I'm so proud of you
Every time I'm so proud of you
It was over in a second.
I wasn't nervous, not really.
I was afraid that I might make a big mistake.
I had that kind of nervousness, but once I got on stage
But once I got on stage, it all happened so fast
I don't remember much about it.
I don't remember too much about it, but I think it was a lot of fun.
And I'm glad if the people who saw me on stage today were even a little bit interested in Tsubaki.
Thank you!
I was lucky to be able to see the camellia twice this time. This person is the same. Um, someone who won a lot of DUOs, and also a lot of Nita cabbages and so on,
How can I put it, was it reassuring?
There were a lot of people who started from the same starting point as us, and they were shining,
But I was a little nervous because it was the last show, but it was fun.
I was really nervous, but before I left, I hugged Luno, I was really nervous, but before I left the stage, I hugged Luno-chan,
After that, I stood up in front of the audience,
When I stood up in front of the audience, the first thing they did was to say, “Oh, wow” when the intro music started playing,
I think that gave me a lot of power to do my best. It was a lot of fun.
Yes, I just watched the making of the show, and I was watching from offstage on the day of the show, and the unison of Okamura-san and Yofu Runo-chan's voices was so beautiful and cool.
The overlap of Okamura-san and Yofu Runo-chan's voices in unison was really beautiful and cool, and the way they expressed themselves was different.
I was attracted by the way they expressed themselves and the way they were different from each other.
She was shining so brightly even though she was standing alone on that big stage with her long arms and legs.
It was a cool and powerful performance.
I think Yofuruno and Minami Okamura have their own image of idols.
Each of them has their own image of an idol.
I felt that each of them had established their own idol image or what they wanted to express.
It was really interesting to see the chemical reaction when they were combined.
Mari Fukuda also looks great on stage.
And Mari Fukuda looked so nervous in the rehearsal and in the interview earlier.
I was more afraid that I might make a mistake.
I had practiced hard, but you never know what might happen on stage, so there was a lot of pressure.
I'm sure there was a lot of pressure on you, but you were able to overcome it with a great performance.
I was so impressed by their performance. This is the making of Hello Project Hina Fest 2024.
That was the making of Hello Project Hina Fest 2024.
Thanks to you, I can do my best!
This is Upcami, featuring Miyoshi Hirai of beyond Seasonings and Wakana Matsumoto of Angulum.
Next up is Tsubaki Factory Power Flower Now is the time to be an eye! Vocal Recording
We'll be back with another episode from Tsubaki Factory's latest album, “Power Flower: Now is the time to be an eye”. Here's a look at Ami Tanimoto's vocal recording.
Are the headphones okay?
Yes.
Yes. Okay, let's start recording.
Okay. Okay, let's record it. Your words that keep illuminating.
It's basically okay.
Let's give it a little more rhythm.
Your figure is dignified, graceful and beautiful
A dream I want to make bloom all over the world
I can't do it alone
I can't make it happen alone
Now's the time
Okay, let's move on.
Okay, let's move on.Yes, sir.
Red, redder, redder. Keep shining your light.
Now is the time to come together
♪ We're moving forward together
To a place you've never seen before
Power Flower
Now is the time to come together
♪ We're moving forward as one
To a place you've never seen before
Power Flower
Yes, that's the feeling
Because the flowers are a little bit faster Power Flower Yes, that's the feeling Because the flowers are a little bit faster
Power Flower
Let's try to fit it in a little bit... in the right place
I'll keep shining redder and redder on you
Now is the time to be consistent
Let's move forward together
To places you've never seen before
Power Flower Now's the time to be consistent, to move forward with your mind together, to go where you've never gone before.
Power Flower Now is the time to be consistent
Now is the time to be consistent, to move forward with all your heart, to turn where you've never turned before
Power Flower
Okay, okay, one, two, three, starting with the moomen part.
First half. We're going this far.
If you don't go faster, you'll sound like a very calm rapper.
Is this a rehearsal? If you don't do it like that, he's a very calm rapper. Is it a rehearsal?
Also, I'd like to see the movement
Movement.
You have to be a little clearer there.
But from the entrance...
One to three.
One to three... and the movement begins...
It's bumpy and clutching now.
I'm clutching at you right now.
ok, let's move on to the next one.
Perfectly unfixed love is an accidental latch-in
Sitting down and sending out a message
more curious than far awayMore curious than far away
Ethereal turns are movies
Paints tomorrow with determination
A little bit is not enough
The destination to be retrieved is clear
Paint tomorrow
Painting tomorrow, that's the rhythm
An ethereal turn is a movie
I draw tomorrow with determination, that's the rhythm, the edgy turn is the smile, I draw tomorrow with determination
A character that won't be daunted by a little bit of drifting
The destination is clear!
Let's go up and up and up.
OK, let's move on.
The rap at the bottom of the 2A
The music in the rap section of the 2A below that.
It's like, “You wouldn't even know if you skipped one of these.
You didn't even notice it.
Shame-shame-shame.
I'm aware of it.
Aso Movie
Aso MovieThat's the thing... the tension is great, but I'm aware of it! Playful painting! Playful painting!
I like the tension, but the rhythm is a bit slow... can you try a tighter, sharper rhythm?
Curiosity rather than fear
Osei
English
paint tomorrow
take out the results
make up
Let's just take a picture of tomorrow
Timing
English angle
Draw tomorrow
I'll paint tomorrow.
The position of the “A” is not good.
I'm glad you enjoyed it... and I'm glad you enjoyed it... and I'm glad you enjoyed it.
I thought the rap part “Fuwari” was very difficult.
But because of your voice, it has an energetic quality.But it's Tanimoto-san's voice that gives it that energetic feeling.
But I also got the feeling that your voice is energetic because it's Tanimoto's.
I thought it was very beautiful.
The chorus of this song is very powerful
You have to use a lot of breath to sing the chorus.
It takes a lot of energy just to sing it.
And the dancing is also very intense.
That's why I was so impressed with your cool performance.
I felt again that Tsubaki Factory is amazing to perform this song so coolly.
That's all for Tsubaki Factory Power Flower!
Now is the time to unite as one!
This is Ami Tanimoto's vocal recording.
Beyond Hi2 Diamond Now on sale
Let's work hard tomorrow!
Hirai Miyo and
Wakana Matsumoto have brought you APKAMI
It's time to say goodbye!
We've seen a lot of videos this time.
I, Matsumoto, saw the first one of Juice Juice's
Juice Juice's “making of” for the music view of “Aiko”.
Juice-san did a triple A-side this time, and all three songs are totally different from each other.
All three songs are totally different from each other and have different coolness.
The song “Oaiko” has a laid-back feeling, but at the same time, it's cool.
I felt once again how cool JuiceJuice is in expressing such a difficult aspect.
I, Hirai, thought that Minamichan Wakamura of Beyond, who was working hard as a shuffle unit, was very cool,
Actually, I was there to watch the rehearsal. I was actually there watching the rehearsal in person.
I saw her and Yof Reno discussing how to do the legs together.
I felt that he had matured a lot.
I knew that our relationship at BEYOND Tomorrows had not changed over the years.
Seeing her like that, I felt that she had become a senior and an adult.
I felt very encouraged.
At Apkami, you can get a behind-the-scenes look at the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally see, so please subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time on Apkami
I'll be talking with Michiyo Hirai of Beyonce Seasonings
Hirai Miyo of Beyonce Seasonings and Angelem'sMiyo Hirai and Angulum's
Wakana Matsumoto.
Good bye.
Next time on Apkami
Beyonce's High to Diamond
Making of music video shooting
And Juice Juice
The recording of Tokyo Gurah
recording session of Tokyo Gurrah.
Enjoy!
Let's go see it!